ground Truth where no real movement is
made um you get an uneasy feeling and I
think a lot of people in this world have
relentlessly felt this uneasy feeling a
desire to communicate
properly what emotion you're feeling and
in struggling to see how easy your ideas
get throt away for people's fear of it
being outside of Overton window or for
fear of
of everything of losing their job of
losing their family of hurting their
children or anything you can get to make
someone feel fear about expressing a
truth that they can quantitatively see
in their experienced life if we can
Empower people people to communicate
effectively that's how you start to
untangle the carpet man that's how you
you got to do the hippie Voice or
whatever that's that's the key is if you
can't trace your head headphone wire in
this Tangled Rat's Nest you're never
going to pull the right wire to even
start to untangle the mess and that's